

Vlad Moisei

Software Developer - SC Diginesis SRL

Remote (from home)

Contact details

Email: vladmoisei@yahoo.com

Tel: +40727385743

City: Calarasi

About me

Software developer with over 5 years of experience in C#, specialized in .NET 9, Blazor, and SQL Server. Involved in large-scale CRM projects with a focus on web and desktop application development, API services, and business logic implementation.

Professional experience

Ex	pe	rier	ıce	by
de	pa	rtm	en	ts

IT Software: 5 years and 3 months

Automation: 10 years and 6 months

Jul 2021 - present

Software Developer - SC Diginesis SRL

4 years and 2 months

Remote (from home) | IT Software | IT / Telecom

I am participating to the development of a big CRM project. I develop Server Services, APIs, Web Components in Blazor, Web Services. Technologies used:

.Net8, C#, Blazor, SQL Server, GitLab.

Acquired skills and competencies:

C#, SQL, git/github, .NET, .Net Framework, .Net Core, blazor

Jun 2020 - Jul 2021

Technical Department Specialist - AFV Beltrame Group

1 year and 2 months

Calarasi | IT Software | Manufacturing

I developed, maintained and extend software applications in .NET Framework to

different departments' needs.

I did improvements in the existing PLC's software to production's needs.

Acquired skills and competencies:

JavaScript, SQL, ASP.NET MVC, HTML / CSS, .Net Core, blazor

Jul 2012 - Jun 2020

Automation engineer - AFV Beltrame Group

8 years

Calarasi | Automation | Manufacturing

- I have configured the existing PLC's, HMI and DC/ AC Drivers (Siemens Micromaster Series, Sinamics, G 120; ABB; EEI) for the needs of production.

www.ejobs.ro CV Vlad Moisei 1/3

- I have fixed faults in the electrical system in the shortest amount of time, improving the production efficiency to 95%.
- I have developed software (Siemens Step 7, WinCC, WinCC Flexible, TIA Portal) for different projects.
- I did commissioning to new drives (Siemens Micro Master Series, G 120) for different projects.
- I have implemented new asp.net applications for different reports on machines / production line.
- I have developed, maintained and extended software applications in .NET Framework to different departments' needs
- I did improvements in the existing PLC's software to production's needs
- I did industrial electrical and controls troubleshooting
- I did PLC and HMI programming

Acquired skills and competencies:

SAP, Microsoft Office, WinCC, WinCC Flexible, siemens step 7, tia portal

Jan 2010 - Jul 2012

Maintenance Engineer - Saint Gobain Glass Romania

2 years and 7 months

Calarasi | Automation | Manufacturing

Saint Gobain Glass Romania Maintenance, Automation engineer Calarasi| Saint Gobain

- Found faults in the automation/ electrical system and fixed them in the shortest amount of time.
- Configured the existing PLC/ DCS system according to the new installed equipment or with the production's needs.
- Ensured that all the instrumentation's equipment was certified every year.
- Completed the preventive maintenance plan with an efficiency of 100% and ensured the stock for spare parts, by ordering them in SAP.

Acquired skills and competencies:

SAP, Microsoft Office, siemens step 7, yokogawa centum 3000

Education

2005 - 2009 Bachelor's degree - UPB University of Mechanical Engineering and

Mechatronics

Mechatronics | Bucharest

2000 - 2004 High School / Vocational school - Mihai Eminescu

Informatics | Calarasi

Skills

General skills

Persoana ambitioasa, modelling softwares - catia, soccer, C#, JavaScript, HTML5/CSS3, WPF, SQL, c/ c++, ReactJS, SolidWorks, AutoCAD 3d, AutoCAD 2d, microsoft word, Graphics, microsoft outlook, AutoCAD, C++, microsoft windows, Microsoft Office, Hard worker, Music, Social skills and competences, microsoft powerpoint, good knowledge, microsoft access, siemens step 7, WinCC, WinCC Flexible, SAP, Catia, starter, tia portal, serious and team player, basic programming in php

www.ejobs.ro CV Vlad Moisei 2/3

Foreign languages

English: Advanced Italian: Advanced

Other sections

Certifications CISCO IT Essentials

date acquired Jan 2017

Driving license Category B

date acquired 13 Nov 2003

www.ejobs.ro contact@ejobs.ro CV Vlad Moisei 3/3